Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public services records, 1968-2005; 1997-2005; Accession 2005-A-043
  - Reference correspondence [filed by fiscal year, then alphabetically by requester's surname]
    - Loe -Lyo, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 589)
    - McA -McM, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 590)
    - Mac -Mar, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 591)
    - Mas -May, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 592)
    - Mea -Mit, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 593)
    - Mog -Mou, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 594)
    - Mud -Mye, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 595)
    - Nag -Nys, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 596)
    - O, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 597)
    - Pac -Pay, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 598)
    - Pea -Piw, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 599)
    - Pla -Pot, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 600)
    - Pow -Qui, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 601)
    - Ran -Rey, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 602)
    - Rhi -Riv, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 603)
    - Roa -Ryd, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 604)
    - Sab -Sav, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 605)
    - Scha -Sco, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 606)
    - Sea -Shu, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 607)
    - Sie -Smi, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 608)
    - Sny -Sri, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 609)
    - Stan -Stau, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 610)
    - Ste -Sti, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 611)
    - Sto -Sze, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 612)
    - Tab -Thu, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 613)
    - Tic -Tzo, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 614)
    - Uli -Von, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 615)
    - Wad -Way, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 616)
    - Wea -Whi, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 617)
    - Wid -Wit, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 618)
    - Wog -Wym, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 619)
    - Xu -Zin, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 620)
    - Aa -Av, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 621)
    - Bab -Baz, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 622)
    - Bea -Blu, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 623)
    - Bly -By, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 624)
    - Ca -Cha, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 625)
    - Che -Con, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 626)
    - Coo-Cu, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 627)
    - Da -Den, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 628)
    - Der -Du, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 629)
    - E, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 630)
    - Fa -For, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 631)
    - Fos -Fu, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 632)
    - Ga -Gon, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 633)
    - Goo -Gwy, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 634)
    - Ha -Har, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 635)
    - Has -Hig, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 636)
    - Hil -Hym, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 637)
    - I, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 638)
    - J, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 639)
    - Ka -Kid, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 640)
    - Kil -Kyv, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 641)
    - La -Led, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 642)
    - Lee -Lip, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 643)
    - Lis -Lyd, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 644)
    - Ma -Mat, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 645)
    - Maw -Mc, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 646)
    - Me -Mond, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 647)
    - Mont -Mut, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 648)
    - N, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 649)
    - O, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 650)
    - Pa -Pf, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 651)
    - Ph -Pu, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 652)
    - Q, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 653)
    - Ra -Rei, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 654)
    - Rem -Roo, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 655)
    - Ros -Ry, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 656)
    - S -Sc, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 657)
    - Se -Sm, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 658)
    - Sn -Sz, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 659)
    - T -U, 2004-2005 (Box 20, Folder 660)
    - V, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 661)
    - Wa -Wen, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 662)
    - Wer -Wy, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 663)
    - Y, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 664)
    - Z, 2004-2005 (Box 21, Folder 665)
  - Subject correspondence [reference]
    - General
      - A, 1969-1988 (Box 21, Folder 666)
      - B, 1970-1989 (Box 21, Folder 667)
      - C, 1965, 1971-1988 (Box 21, Folder 668)
      - D -E, 1970-1988 (Box 21, Folder 669)
      - F -G, 1971-1989 (Box 21, Folder 670)
      - H, 1971-1988 (Box 21, Folder 671)
      - I -K, 1970-1988 (Box 21, Folder 672)
      - L, 1966, 1970-1989 (Box 21, Folder 673)
      - M -N, 1965-1989 (Box 21, Folder 674)
      - O -P, 1969-1989 (Box 21, Folder 675)
      - Q -R, 1970-1989 (Box 21, Folder 676)
      - S, 1969-1989 (Box 21, Folder 677)
      - T -V, 1970-1988 (Box 21, Folder 678)
      - W -Z, 1969-1989 (Box 21, Folder 679)
    - Yale Biography
      - A -B, 1982-1988 (Box 21, Folder 680)
      - C -D, 1981-1988 (Box 21, Folder 681)
      - E -F, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 682)
      - G -H, 1981-1988 (Box 21, Folder 683)
      - I -J, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 684)
      - K -L, 1984-1988 (Box 21, Folder 685)
      - M -N, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 686)
      - O -P, 1983-1989 (Box 21, Folder 687)
      - Q -R, 1985-1988 (Box 21, Folder 688)
      - S -T, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 689)
      - U -V, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 690)
      - W -X, 1983-1988 (Box 21, Folder 691)
      - Y -Z, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 692)
    - Yale History, 1960-1990 (Box 21, Folder 693)
    - Dissertations [filed alphabetically by surname of dissertation author]
      - A -F, 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 694)
      - G -M, 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 695)
      - N -Z, 1993-2000 (Box 21, Folder 696)
    - Numismatics Collection, 1996-2000 (Box 21, Folder 697)
    - Manuscript collections [copies of reference correspondence relating to individual collections,], circa 1968-2000
      - MS 1 (Box 22, Folder 698)
      - MS 2 (Box 22, Folder 699)
      - MS 3 (Box 22, Folder 700)
      - MS 4 (Box 22, Folder 701)
      - MS 5 (Box 22, Folder 702)
      - MS 6 (Box 22, Folder 703)
      - MS 7 (Box 22, Folder 704)
      - MS 8 (Box 22, Folder 705)
      - MS 9 (Box 22, Folder 706)
      - MS 10 (Box 22, Folder 707)
      - MS 11 (Box 22, Folder 708)
      - MS 12 (Box 22, Folder 709)
      - MS 14 (Box 22, Folder 710)
      - MS 16 (Box 22, Folder 711)
      - MS 18 (Box 22, Folder 712)
      - MS 19 (Box 22, Folder 713)
      - MS 21 (Box 22, Folder 714)
      - MS 23 (Box 22, Folder 715)
      - MS 24 (Box 22, Folder 716)
      - MS 25 (Box 22, Folder 717)
      - MS 26 (Box 22, Folder 718)
      - MS 27 (Box 22, Folder 719)
      - MS 28 (Box 22, Folder 720)
      - MS 29 (Box 22, Folder 721)
      - MS 30 (Box 22, Folder 722)
      - MS 31 (Box 22, Folder 723)
      - MS 32 (Box 22, Folder 724)
      - MS 33 (Box 22, Folder 725)
      - MS 34 (Box 22, Folder 726)
      - MS 35 (Box 22, Folder 727)
      - MS 36 (Box 22, Folder 728)
      - MS 37 (Box 22, Folder 729)
      - MS 38 (Box 22, Folder 730)
      - MS 39 (Box 22, Folder 731)
      - MS 40 (Box 22, Folder 732)
      - MS 41 (Box 22, Folder 733)
      - MS 42 (Box 22, Folder 734)
      - MS 44 (Box 22, Folder 735)
      - MS 46 (Box 22, Folder 736)
      - MS 47 (Box 22, Folder 737)
      - MS 49 (Box 22, Folder 738)
      - MS 51 (Box 22, Folder 739)
      - MS 52 (Box 22, Folder 740)
      - MS 53 (Box 22, Folder 741)
      - MS 54 (Box 22, Folder 742)
      - MS 55 (Box 22, Folder 743)
      - MS 58 (Box 22, Folder 744)
      - MS 59 (Box 22, Folder 745)
      - MS 60 (Box 22, Folder 746)
      - MS 62 (Box 22, Folder 747)
      - MS 64 (Box 22, Folder 748)
      - MS 65 (Box 22, Folder 749)
      - MS 66 (Box 22, Folder 750)
      - MS 68 (Box 22, Folder 751)
      - MS 71 (Box 22, Folder 752)
      - MS 73 (Box 22, Folder 753)
      - MS 74 (Box 22, Folder 754)
      - MS 75 (Box 22, Folder 755)
      - MS 76 (Box 22, Folder 756)
      - MS 77 (Box 22, Folder 757)
      - MS 79 (Box 22, Folder 758)
      - MS 81 (Box 22, Folder 759)
      - MS 82 (Box 22, Folder 760)
      - MS 83 (Box 22, Folder 761)
      - MS 85 (Box 22, Folder 762)
      - MS 88 (Box 22, Folder 763)
      - MS 89 (Box 22, Folder 764)
      - MS 90 (Box 22, Folder 765)
      - MS 92 (Box 22, Folder 766)
      - MS 94 (Box 22, Folder 767)
      - MS 95 (Box 22, Folder 768)
      - MS 96 (Box 22, Folder 769)
      - MS 99 (Box 22, Folder 770)
      - MS 100 (Box 22, Folder 771)
      - MS 103 (Box 22, Folder 772)
      - MS 104 (Box 22, Folder 773)
      - MS 105 (Box 22, Folder 774)
      - MS 106 (Box 22, Folder 775)
      - MS 107 (Box 22, Folder 776)
      - MS 108 (Box 22, Folder 777)
      - MS 110 (Box 22, Folder 778)
      - MS 112 (Box 22, Folder 779)
      - MS 113 (Box 22, Folder 780)
      - MS 114 (Box 22, Folder 781)
      - MS 115 (Box 22, Folder 782)
      - MS 116 (Box 22, Folder 783)
      - MS 117 (Box 22, Folder 784)
      - MS 118 (Box 22, Folder 785)
      - MS 120 (Box 22, Folder 786)
      - MS 121 (Box 22, Folder 787)
      - MS 123 (Box 22, Folder 788)
      - MS 124 (Box 22, Folder 789)
      - MS 125 (Box 22, Folder 790)
      - MS 126 (Box 22, Folder 791)
      - MS 128 (Box 22, Folder 792)
      - MS 129 (Box 22, Folder 793)
      - MS 130 (Box 22, Folder 794)
      - MS 133 (Box 22, Folder 795)
      - MS 134 (Box 22, Folder 796)
      - MS 135 (Box 22, Folder 797)
      - MS 137 (Box 22, Folder 798)
      - MS 138 (Box 22, Folder 799)
      - MS 139 (Box 22, Folder 800)
      - MS 140 (Box 22, Folder 801)
      - MS 141 (Box 22, Folder 802)
      - MS 143 (Box 22, Folder 803)
      - MS 144 (Box 22, Folder 804)
      - MS 146 (Box 22, Folder 805)
      - MS 147 (Box 22, Folder 806)
      - MS 148 (Box 22, Folder 807)
      - MS 149 (Box 22, Folder 808)
      - MS 150 (Box 22, Folder 809)
      - MS 152 (Box 22, Folder 810)
      - MS 153 (Box 22, Folder 811)
      - MS 155 (Box 22, Folder 812)
      - MS 159 (Box 22, Folder 813)
      - MS 160 (Box 22, Folder 814)
      - MS 161 (Box 22, Folder 815)
      - MS 162 (Box 22, Folder 816)
      - MS 163 (Box 22, Folder 817)
      - MS 164 (Box 22, Folder 818)
      - MS 165 (Box 22, Folder 819)
      - MS 168 (Box 22, Folder 820)
      - MS 169 (Box 22, Folder 821)
      - MS 170 (Box 23, Folder 822)
      - MS 171 (Box 23, Folder 823)
      - MS 173 (Box 23, Folder 824)
      - MS 175 (Box 23, Folder 825)
      - MS 176 (Box 23, Folder 826)
      - MS 178 (Box 23, Folder 827)
      - MS 179 (Box 23, Folder 828)
      - MS 180 (Box 23, Folder 829)
      - MS 181 (Box 23, Folder 830)
      - MS 183 (Box 23, Folder 831)
      - MS 184 (Box 23, Folder 832)
      - MS 187 (Box 23, Folder 833)
      - MS 189 (Box 23, Folder 834)
      - MS 190 (Box 23, Folder 835)
      - MS 191 (Box 23, Folder 836)
      - MS 192 (Box 23, Folder 837)
      - MS 193 (Box 23, Folder 838)
      - MS 194 (Box 23, Folder 839)
      - MS 195 (Box 23, Folder 840)
      - MS 196 (Box 23, Folder 841)
      - MS 198 (Box 23, Folder 842)
      - MS 200 (Box 23, Folder 843)
      - MS 201 (Box 23, Folder 844)
      - MS 202 (Box 23, Folder 845)
      - MS 203 (Box 23, Folder 846)
      - MS 204 (Box 23, Folder 847)
      - MS 205 (Box 23, Folder 848)
      - MS 206 (Box 23, Folder 849)
      - MS 207 (Box 23, Folder 850)
      - MS 208 (Box 23, Folder 851)
      - MS 209 (Box 23, Folder 852)
      - MS 212 (Box 23, Folder 853)
      - MS 214 (Box 23, Folder 854)
      - MS 215 (Box 23, Folder 855)
      - MS 216 (Box 23, Folder 856)
      - MS 218 (Box 23, Folder 857)
      - MS 219 (Box 23, Folder 858)
      - MS 221 (Box 23, Folder 859)
      - MS 222 (Box 23, Folder 860)
      - MS 223 (Box 23, Folder 861)
      - MS 224 (Box 23, Folder 862)
      - MS 226 (Box 23, Folder 863)
      - MS 227 (Box 23, Folder 864)
      - MS 228 (Box 23, Folder 865)
      - MS 229 (Box 23, Folder 866)
      - MS 230 (Box 23, Folder 867)
      - MS 231 (Box 23, Folder 868)
      - MS 232 (Box 23, Folder 869)
      - MS 234 (Box 23, Folder 870)
      - MS 235 (Box 23, Folder 871)
      - MS 236 (Box 23, Folder 872)
      - MS 237 (Box 23, Folder 873)
      - MS 238 (Box 23, Folder 874)
      - MS 239 (Box 23, Folder 875)
      - MS 240 (Box 23, Folder 876)
      - MS 241 (Box 23, Folder 877)
      - MS 242 (Box 23, Folder 878)
      - MS 243 (Box 23, Folder 879)
      - MS 244 (Box 23, Folder 880)
      - MS 245 (Box 23, Folder 881)
      - MS 246 (Box 23, Folder 882)
      - MS 247 (Box 23, Folder 883)
      - MS 248 (Box 23, Folder 884)
      - MS 249 (Box 23, Folder 885)
      - MS 250 (Box 23, Folder 886)
      - MS 251 (Box 23, Folder 887)
      - MS 254 (Box 23, Folder 888)
      - MS 255 (Box 23, Folder 889)
      - MS 256 (Box 23, Folder 890)
      - MS 257 (Box 23, Folder 891)
      - MS 258 (Box 23, Folder 892)
      - MS 259 (Box 23, Folder 893)
      - MS 262 (Box 23, Folder 894)
      - MS 263 (Box 23, Folder 895)
      - MS 265 (Box 23, Folder 896)
      - MS 268 (Box 23, Folder 897)
      - MS 269 (Box 23, Folder 898)
      - MS 270 (Box 23, Folder 899)
      - MS 271 (Box 23, Folder 900)
      - MS 275 (Box 23, Folder 901)
      - MS 278 (Box 23, Folder 902)
      - MS 280 (Box 23, Folder 903)
      - MS 281 (Box 23, Folder 904)
      - MS 282 (Box 23, Folder 905)
      - MS 284 (Box 23, Folder 906)
      - MS 285 (Box 23, Folder 907)
      - MS 286 (Box 23, Folder 908)
      - MS 287 (Box 23, Folder 909)
      - MS 288 (Box 23, Folder 910)
      - MS 289 (Box 23, Folder 911)
      - MS 290 (Box 23, Folder 912)
      - MS 291 (Box 23, Folder 913)
      - MS 291A (Box 23, Folder 914)
      - MS 292 (Box 23, Folder 915)
      - MS 294 (Box 23, Folder 916)
      - MS 295 (Box 23, Folder 917)
      - MS 296 (Box 23, Folder 918)
      - MS 297 (Box 23, Folder 919)
      - MS 299 (Box 23, Folder 920)
      - MS 301 (Box 23, Folder 921)
      - MS 303 (Box 23, Folder 922)
      - MS 304 (Box 23, Folder 923)
      - MS 305 (Box 23, Folder 924)
      - MS 307 (Box 23, Folder 925)
      - MS 308 (Box 23, Folder 926)
      - MS 309 (Box 23, Folder 927)
      - MS 310 (Box 23, Folder 928)
      - MS 311 (Box 23, Folder 929)
      - MS 312 (Box 23, Folder 930)
      - MS 314 (Box 23, Folder 931)
      - MS 315 (Box 23, Folder 932)
      - MS 316 (Box 23, Folder 933)
      - MS 317 (Box 23, Folder 934)
      - MS 318 (Box 23, Folder 935)
      - MS 320 (Box 23, Folder 936)
      - MS 321 (Box 23, Folder 937)
      - MS 322 (Box 23, Folder 938)
      - MS 325 (Box 23, Folder 939)
      - MS 325B (Box 23, Folder 940)
      - MS 326 (Box 23, Folder 941 - 943)
      - MS 327 (Box 24, Folder 944)
      - MS 328 (Box 24, Folder 945)
      - MS 330 (Box 24, Folder 946)
      - MS 331 (Box 24, Folder 947)
      - MS 332 (Box 24, Folder 948)
      - MS 333 (Box 24, Folder 949)
      - MS 334 (Box 24, Folder 950)
      - MS 335 (Box 24, Folder 951)
      - MS 337 (Box 24, Folder 952)
      - MS 338 (Box 24, Folder 953)
      - MS 339 (Box 24, Folder 954)
      - MS 340 (Box 24, Folder 955)
      - MS 341 (Box 24, Folder 956)
      - MS 343 (Box 24, Folder 957)
      - MS 344 (Box 24, Folder 958)
      - MS 345 (Box 24, Folder 959)
      - MS 348 (Box 24, Folder 960)
      - MS 349 (Box 24, Folder 961)
      - MS 350 (Box 24, Folder 962)
      - MS 352 (Box 24, Folder 963)
      - MS 353 (Box 24, Folder 964)
      - MS 354 (Box 24, Folder 965)
      - MS 356 (Box 24, Folder 966)
      - MS 358 (Box 24, Folder 967)
      - MS 359 (Box 24, Folder 968)
      - MS 361 (Box 24, Folder 969)
      - MS 362 (Box 24, Folder 970)
      - MS 363 (Box 24, Folder 971)
      - MS 364 (Box 24, Folder 972)
      - MS 365 (Box 24, Folder 973)
      - MS 366 (Box 24, Folder 974)
      - MS 367 (Box 24, Folder 975)
      - MS 370 (Box 24, Folder 976)
      - MS 371 (Box 24, Folder 977)
      - MS 375 (Box 24, Folder 978)
      - MS 376 (Box 24, Folder 979)
      - MS 377 (Box 24, Folder 980)
      - MS 382 (Box 24, Folder 981)
      - MS 384 (Box 24, Folder 982)
      - MS 387 (Box 24, Folder 983)
      - MS 389 (Box 24, Folder 984)
      - MS 390 (Box 24, Folder 985)
      - MS 391 (Box 24, Folder 986)
      - MS 392 (Box 24, Folder 987)
      - MS 394 (Box 24, Folder 988)
      - MS 396 (Box 24, Folder 989)
      - MS 397 (Box 24, Folder 990)
      - MS 398 (Box 24, Folder 991)
      - MS 399 (Box 24, Folder 992)
      - MS 400 (Box 24, Folder 993)
      - MS 401 (Box 24, Folder 994)
      - MS 402 (Box 24, Folder 995)
      - MS 403 (Box 24, Folder 996)
      - MS 404 (Box 24, Folder 997)
      - MS 405 (Box 24, Folder 998)
      - MS 406 (Box 24, Folder 999)
      - MS 409 (Box 24, Folder 1000)
      - MS 411 (Box 24, Folder 1001)
      - MS 413 (Box 24, Folder 1002)
      - MS 415 (Box 24, Folder 1003)
      - MS 416 (Box 24, Folder 1004)
      - MS 417 (Box 24, Folder 1005)
      - MS 421 (Box 24, Folder 1006)
      - MS 423 (Box 24, Folder 1007)
      - MS 424 (Box 24, Folder 1008)
      - MS 425 (Box 24, Folder 1009)
      - MS 427 (Box 24, Folder 1010)
      - MS 429 (Box 24, Folder 1011)
      - MS 430 (Box 24, Folder 1012)
      - MS 431 (Box 24, Folder 1013)
      - MS 432 (Box 24, Folder 1014)
      - MS 433 (Box 24, Folder 1015)
      - MS 434 (Box 24, Folder 1016)
      - MS 435 (Box 24, Folder 1017)
      - MS 437 (Box 24, Folder 1018)
      - MS 438 (Box 24, Folder 1019)
      - MS 440 (Box 24, Folder 1020)
      - MS 441 (Box 24, Folder 1021)
      - MS 442 (Box 24, Folder 1022)
      - MS 444 (Box 24, Folder 1023)
      - MS 445 (Box 24, Folder 1024)
      - MS 446 (Box 24, Folder 1025)
      - MS 447 (Box 24, Folder 1026)
      - MS 448 (Box 24, Folder 1027)
      - MS 449 (Box 24, Folder 1028)
      - MS 450 (Box 24, Folder 1029)
      - MS 452 (Box 24, Folder 1030)
      - MS 453 (Box 24, Folder 1031)
      - MS 455 (Box 24, Folder 1032)
      - MS 456 (Box 24, Folder 1033)
      - MS 458 (Box 24, Folder 1034)
      - MS 461 (Box 24, Folder 1035)
      - MS 465 (Box 24, Folder 1036 - 1039)
      - MS 466 (Box 24, Folder 1040)
      - MS 467 (Box 24, Folder 1041)
      - MS 468 (Box 24, Folder 1042)
      - MS 470 (Box 24, Folder 1043)
      - MS 471 (Box 24, Folder 1044)
      - MS 473 (Box 24, Folder 1045)
      - MS 474 (Box 24, Folder 1046)
      - MS 476 (Box 24, Folder 1047)
      - MS 477 (Box 24, Folder 1048)
      - MS 478 (Box 24, Folder 1049)
      - MS 479 (Box 24, Folder 1050)
      - MS 480 (Box 24, Folder 1051)
      - MS 481 (Box 24, Folder 1052)
      - MS 482 (Box 24, Folder 1053)
      - MS 486 (Box 24, Folder 1054)
      - MS 489 (Box 24, Folder 1055)
      - MS 494 (Box 24, Folder 1056)
      - MS 495 (Box 25, Folder 1057)
      - MS 496 (Box 25, Folder 1058)
      - MS 496A (Box 25, Folder 1059)
      - MS 496B (Box 25, Folder 1060)
      - MS 496C (Box 25, Folder 1061)
      - MS 496D (Box 25, Folder 1062)
      - MS 496E (Box 25, Folder 1063)
      - MS 496F (Box 25, Folder 1064)
      - MS 498 (Box 25, Folder 1065)
      - MS 499 (Box 25, Folder 1066)
      - MS 502 (Box 25, Folder 1067)
      - MS 504 (Box 25, Folder 1068)
      - MS 505 (Box 25, Folder 1069)
      - MS 506 (Box 25, Folder 1070)
      - MS 507 (Box 25, Folder 1071)
      - MS 508 (Box 25, Folder 1072)
      - MS 509 (Box 25, Folder 1073)
      - MS 510 (Box 25, Folder 1074)
      - MS 511 (Box 25, Folder 1075)
      - MS 512 (Box 25, Folder 1076)
      - MS 514 (Box 25, Folder 1077)
      - MS 515 (Box 25, Folder 1078)
      - MS 516 (Box 25, Folder 1079)
      - MS 519 (Box 25, Folder 1080)
      - MS 520 (Box 25, Folder 1081)
      - MS 521 (Box 25, Folder 1082)
      - MS 522 (Box 25, Folder 1083)
      - MS 523 (Box 25, Folder 1084)
      - MS 524 (Box 25, Folder 1085)
      - MS 525 (Box 25, Folder 1086)
      - MS 526 (Box 25, Folder 1087)
      - MS 527 (Box 25, Folder 1088)
      - MS 528 (Box 25, Folder 1089)
      - MS 529 (Box 25, Folder 1090)
      - MS 533 (Box 25, Folder 1091)
      - MS 535 (Box 25, Folder 1092)
      - MS 538 (Box 25, Folder 1093)
      - MS 539 (Box 25, Folder 1094)
      - MS 540 (Box 25, Folder 1095)
      - MS 541 (Box 25, Folder 1096)
      - MS 542 (Box 25, Folder 1097)
      - MS 543 (Box 25, Folder 1098)
      - MS 544 (Box 25, Folder 1099)
      - MS 545 (Box 25, Folder 1100)
      - MS 546 (Box 25, Folder 1101)
      - MS 547 (Box 25, Folder 1102)
      - MS 548 (Box 25, Folder 1103)
      - MS 549 (Box 25, Folder 1104)
      - MS 550 (Box 25, Folder 1105)
      - MS 552 (Box 25, Folder 1106)
      - MS 553 (Box 25, Folder 1107)
      - MS 554 (Box 25, Folder 1108)
      - MS 555 (Box 25, Folder 1109)
      - MS 556 (Box 25, Folder 1110)
      - MS 558 (Box 25, Folder 1111)
      - MS 559 (Box 25, Folder 1112)
      - MS 560 (Box 25, Folder 1113)
      - MS 562 (Box 25, Folder 1114)
      - MS 564 (Box 25, Folder 1115)
      - MS 565 (Box 25, Folder 1116)
      - MS 566 (Box 25, Folder 1117)
      - MS 567 (Box 25, Folder 1118)
      - MS 568 (Box 25, Folder 1119)
      - MS 569 (Box 25, Folder 1120)
      - MS 572 (Box 25, Folder 1121)
      - MS 573 (Box 25, Folder 1122)
      - MS 574 (Box 25, Folder 1123)
      - MS 575 (Box 25, Folder 1124)
      - MS 576 (Box 25, Folder 1125)
      - MS 578 (Box 25, Folder 1126)
      - MS 579 (Box 25, Folder 1127)
      - MS 580 (Box 25, Folder 1128)
      - MS 581 (Box 25, Folder 1129)
      - MS 582 (Box 25, Folder 1130)
      - MS 583 (Box 25, Folder 1131)
      - MS 584 (Box 25, Folder 1132)
      - MS 587 (Box 25, Folder 1133)
      - MS 589 (Box 25, Folder 1134)
      - MS 590 (Box 25, Folder 1135)
      - MS 591 (Box 25, Folder 1136)
      - MS 592 (Box 25, Folder 1137)
      - MS 593 (Box 25, Folder 1138)
      - MS 595 (Box 25, Folder 1139)
      - MS 596 (Box 25, Folder 1140)
      - MS 598 (Box 25, Folder 1141)
      - MS 599 (Box 25, Folder 1142)
      - MS 600 (Box 25, Folder 1143)
      - MS 601 (Box 25, Folder 1144)
      - MS 602 (Box 25, Folder 1145)
      - MS 603 (Box 25, Folder 1146)
      - MS 604 (Box 25, Folder 1147)
      - MS 605 (Box 25, Folder 1148)
      - MS 606 (Box 25, Folder 1149)
      - MS 607 (Box 25, Folder 1150)
      - MS 609 (Box 25, Folder 1151)
      - MS 611 (Box 25, Folder 1152)
      - MS 612 (Box 25, Folder 1153)
      - MS 613 (Box 25, Folder 1154)
      - MS 615 (Box 25, Folder 1155)
      - MS 616 (Box 25, Folder 1156)
      - MS 618 (Box 25, Folder 1157)
      - MS 619 (Box 25, Folder 1158)
      - MS 620 (Box 25, Folder 1159)
      - MS 621 (Box 25, Folder 1160)
      - MS 622 (Box 25, Folder 1161)
      - MS 623 (Box 25, Folder 1162)
      - MS 624 (Box 25, Folder 1163)
      - MS 625 (Box 25, Folder 1164)
      - MS 626 (Box 25, Folder 1165)
      - MS 627 (Box 25, Folder 1166)
      - MS 628 (Box 25, Folder 1167)
      - MS 629 (Box 25, Folder 1168)
      - MS 631 (Box 25, Folder 1169)
      - MS 633 (Box 25, Folder 1170)
      - MS 634 (Box 25, Folder 1171)
      - MS 635 (Box 25, Folder 1172)
      - MS 638 (Box 25, Folder 1173)
      - MS 640 (Box 25, Folder 1174)
      - MS 641 (Box 25, Folder 1175)
      - MS 642 (Box 26, Folder 1176)
      - MS 645 (Box 26, Folder 1177)
      - MS 648 (Box 26, Folder 1178)
      - MS 649 (Box 26, Folder 1179)
      - MS 650 (Box 26, Folder 1180)
      - MS 651 (Box 26, Folder 1181)
      - MS 652 (Box 26, Folder 1182)
      - MS 654 (Box 26, Folder 1183)
      - MS 656 (Box 26, Folder 1184)
      - MS 657 (Box 26, Folder 1185)
      - MS 658 (Box 26, Folder 1186)
      - MS 661 (Box 26, Folder 1187)
      - MS 663 (Box 26, Folder 1188)
      - MS 664 (Box 26, Folder 1189)
      - MS 666 (Box 26, Folder 1190)
      - MS 667 (Box 26, Folder 1191)
      - MS 669 (Box 26, Folder 1192)
      - MS 670 (Box 26, Folder 1193)
      - MS 671 (Box 26, Folder 1194)
      - MS 674 (Box 26, Folder 1195)
      - MS 675 (Box 26, Folder 1196)
      - MS 677 (Box 26, Folder 1197)
      - MS 678 (Box 26, Folder 1198)
      - MS 680 (Box 26, Folder 1199)
      - MS 683 (Box 26, Folder 1200)
      - MS 684 (Box 26, Folder 1201)
      - MS 685 (Box 26, Folder 1202)
      - MS 686 (Box 26, Folder 1203)
      - MS 687 (Box 26, Folder 1204)
      - MS 688 (Box 26, Folder 1205)
      - MS 690 (Box 26, Folder 1206)
      - MS 691 (Box 26, Folder 1207)
      - MS 692 (Box 26, Folder 1208)
      - MS 695 (Box 26, Folder 1209)
      - MS 696 (Box 26, Folder 1210)